‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪LAUNDRY HUB
‪What the heck?
‪Don't move, or else we all die!
‪Get down!
‪Get in the cart.
‪Watch out!
‪Come in.
‪So, what happened?
‪Well…
‪They got away.
‪FINALE
‪Head to the stairs.
‪Hold on.
‪What are you doing here?
‪Oh, you're here to save me.
‪Hey, Park Gang Seong.
‪Number 66 is on our side now.
‪Put down your gun.
‪I heard the person
‪who got my brother killed…
‪was you.
‪What…
‪What are you talking about?
‪I told you Park Yeong Gwang was killed
‪by the South Korean bastards
‪-during a mission--
‪-Didn't you say 66 killed him?
‪No, what I meant was…
‪Why are you so quiet?
‪Go ahead and say it wasn't you.
‪I…
‪couldn't save your brother.
‪That's it.
‪Move.
‪I said move!
‪You think doing this will keep you safe?
‪You betrayed the Party's orders as well!
‪I'll talk to the South Korean authorities.
‪You and I can defect together
‪-and find a way to live--
‪-Shut up!
‪Let me ask you one thing.
‪Why are you protecting that enemy bastard?
‪Sang-a.
‪It's okay.
‪To protect my daughter.
‪Protecting the people I care about…
‪is more important…
‪than killing my enemy.
‪You'll get another chance.
‪Trust me and walk away.
‪Hurry up and get in!
‪I was told to move the truck,
‪so I had to circle around.
‪What's going on?
‪Mr. Kim.
‪Let it through.
‪SECURITY CHECK
‪I heard gunshots, and it sounded serious.
‪Did something happen?
‪No, it's nothing serious.
‪It's just an internal issue.
‪-You can leave.
‪-But I have more laundry to pick up.
‪You can do it next time.
‪Please leave for now.
‪We have an urgent situation.
‪-Okay, then. Good night.
‪-Good night.
‪Close the barricades.
‪You can get out now.
‪-Take him to a hospital.
‪-What?
‪But a gunshot wound
‪is hard to keep under wraps.
‪Contact General Jang. He'll help.
‪What happened to Mr. Sung Han-soo
‪and Mr. Park Jin-cheol?
‪I saw them
‪getting into Ju Gang-chan's car.
‪-Ju Gang-chan?
‪-Yeah.
‪Han-soo.
‪Where are you?
‪What's wrong?
‪Kim, I'm sorry.
‪Mr. Kim.
‪Mr. Kim?
‪Let's go.
‪Are you really not going to tell us?
‪Take him to a hospital.
‪Okay.
‪I'm sorry.
‪If you don't come…
‪the kids will die.
‪Please.
‪I'm begging you.
‪I'll be right there.
‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪A FEW HOURS AGO
‪Who are you?
‪Damn it, I just mopped the floor.
‪-It's him.
‪-This is a Taekwondo studio.
‪Take off your shoes first.
‪-Whip it up, whip it up, up and down
‪-Whip it up
‪-Whip it up, whip it up
‪Whip it…
‪What the hell?
‪Are you Da-bin?
‪Yes, that's me.
‪Who are you?
‪Take him.
‪Mister.
‪Why are you doing this to us?
‪Please let us go.
‪Untie us right now!
‪Mister,
‪please let us go.
‪Please!
‪JUHAK CONSTRUCTION CHAIRMAN JU GANG-CHAN
‪Ready, sir.
‪So you're willing to risk your life
‪for your friends' kids.
‪I have to say I'm surprised.
‪Then again, you two did the same.
‪Now you get to choose.
‪Will you kill your friend…
‪or will you kill your kids?
‪I'm really sorry…
‪for dragging you into this.
‪If 66 dies, the kids will live.
‪Do you really have a choice?
‪-No!
‪-Da-bin!
‪-Stop!
‪-Dad!
‪-Father!
‪Dad, please help!
‪Father…
‪I'll do whatever you want, so stop it!
‪Kim.
‪Jin-cheol.
‪Han-soo.
‪You have to take me down…
‪for the kids to live.
‪Get it together!
‪Get up.
‪Kim!
‪There must be a way.
‪Focus on the kids.
‪Focus!
‪Han-soo!
‪Kim.
‪This is a bit of a letdown.
‪You're not taking this seriously.
‪I'll give you five minutes.
‪If you don't kill him by then,
‪I'll shoot the kids myself.
‪Father!
‪-Dad!
‪-Then I'll shoot 66.
‪Please help!
‪Father.
‪-Dad!
‪-Father!
‪Father…
‪What are you waiting for?
‪Your kids are calling for you.
‪Dad!
‪-Father!
‪-Dad!
‪More, more, more!
‪Get up.
‪Get up! I said get up!
‪Get up!
‪Tae-hun…
‪and Da-bin…
‪You have to save them.
‪And…
‪please take care…
‪of Min-ji.
‪How sad,
‪you're going to miss Min-ji so much.
‪Come back.
‪I'll wait for you.
‪You'll come back.
‪You're my dad.
‪One.
‪Two.
‪Three.
‪-Dad!
‪-Uncle!
‪Four.
‪-Damn it.
‪-Get up.
‪Get up! I said get up!
‪Three seconds.
‪Three seconds is enough.
‪-Da-bin!
‪-Dad!
‪Dad, you got shot. Are you okay?
‪-I'm okay. I didn't get shot.
‪-Are you okay?
‪I'm fine.
‪-I dodged it.
‪-Oh, you did?
‪-You didn't get shot?
‪-No, I didn't.
‪Are you okay? You must've been so scared.
‪-My poor Da-bin!
‪-Dad, I'm fine.
‪-If anything had happened to you…
‪-I said I'm fine!
‪Hurry up and free me.
‪Jeez, this is so annoying.
‪-That hurts!
‪-Stop touching my hair!
‪I won't touch your hair.
‪You're okay, you're okay.
‪Yeah, I'm fine.
‪Let's go.
‪Are you okay?
‪-I'm fine.
‪-Can you get up?
‪I'm okay.
‪I'm fine.
‪Kim!
‪You okay?
‪What about the kids?
‪-They're fine.
‪-Are you okay?
‪What do you think?
‪Of course, he's not okay.
‪Right, you got beaten up by us, after all.
‪It took four seconds.
‪That's why he got shot.
‪It just grazed me.
‪-You okay?
‪-What do you think?
‪Of course, he's not okay.
‪He seems okay.
‪Hey, chairman.
‪We have some unfinished business.
‪A parent meeting.
‪What else is there to do?
‪I have to keep my promise.
‪Are you okay to drive?
‪I guess he is.
‪What about the kids?
‪Shouldn't we keep an eye on them
‪so they don't go out?
‪Does Tae-hun ever listen to you?
‪Of course, he doesn't.
‪He even attacks his own father.
‪At least Da-bin doesn't attack me.
‪She just ignores me.
‪We should leave them with someone
‪who can intimidate them.
‪-Like who?
‪-I know someone.
‪Someone scarier than me.
‪Actually, they might be
‪the scariest person on the planet.
‪Let's go.
‪Man, my legs.
‪My poor legs.
‪My legs are killing me.
‪My steering wheel!
‪Come on!
‪SECURITY COMMANDER KANG JI-YEONG
‪Is this a joke?
‪17TH AMPHIBIOUS MOBILE BRIGADE
‪RED DRAGON UNIT SPECIAL SECURITY BATTALION
‪Honey…
‪Would you mind
‪watching the kids for a bit?
‪If you could keep them in a room
‪and protect them for a few days…
‪Please?
‪This isn't a daycare center.
‪You little punk!
‪This is fake. Do you have any guns, lady?
‪I told you not to call me that.
‪Be quiet and go away.
‪Mom, lend me your phone.
‪Da-bin, be quiet.
‪I told you not to get into trouble.
‪I didn't get into trouble.
‪I just felt so bad for Kim
‪that I had no choice but to help.
‪I had no choice
‪because Jin-cheol told me to help.
‪Kim? Again?
‪I ought to just…
‪That's not true.
‪It's not true, honey.
‪I wanted to help him.
‪It was my choice.
‪My friend…
‪had to do one last mission
‪to see his daughter again.
‪So I wanted to help him.
‪Me too.
‪Still, you shouldn't have
‪put the kids in danger.
‪I'm sorry, honey.
‪I'm sorry too.
‪The kids will stay with me.
‪I can't trust you two.
‪-Honey!
‪I mean, Ji-yeong.
‪When will you middle-aged men grow up?
‪Seriously, when will you…
‪When…
‪Honey.
‪Have I told you
‪-that I love--
‪-Get out.
‪-Yes, he has.
‪-Let's go.
‪-Hurry.
‪-Sit properly.
‪Eat as much as you can in one sitting,
‪and don't ask for snacks.
‪-You know what to do, right?
‪-What?
‪And don't ask
‪for the Wi-Fi password, okay?
‪-Why?
‪-Don't ask. Just be quiet.
‪-Got it?
‪-Yeah, just go already.
‪-Don't make her mad.
‪-Okay, okay.
‪All right, attention!
‪Salute!
‪Hands down.
‪Dad.
‪Do as she says.
‪Are you hungry?
‪Yes, I am.
‪Those guys didn't even feed you?
‪What do you want?
‪Want me to order ‪jjajangmyeon‪?
‪INTER-KOREAN GOVERNMENT TALKS
‪I'm pleased that both sides
‪could come to an agreement.
‪I hope that the North and the South
‪can move toward a cooperative future
‪through the free-trade zone.
‪Likewise.
‪Thank you, everyone.
‪Can the two of you please shake hands?
‪I think we have other matters to discuss.
‪About what happened last night, that is.
‪As you know,
‪we've done our best to accommodate
‪the North's requests during this visit.
‪Don't you agree?
‪It was all for the good
‪of inter-Korean cooperation.
‪What are your thoughts, sir?
‪But you know,
‪I think what happened last night
‪was out of line.
‪Shouldn't you take responsibility
‪for causing such a scene
‪on South Korean soil?
‪That was…
‪There was an internal issue.
‪And that issue
‪almost turned South Korea
‪into a battlefield.
‪No, we had no intention of--
‪Now, now.
‪Considering the outcome of these talks,
‪we won't take official retaliatory action
‪against the North.
‪However,
‪let's settle this with the understanding
‪that we have zero responsibility
‪for the casualties on your side.
‪Understood.
‪WE WELCOME THE NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION
‪TO JUHAK HERITAGE RESORT
‪Listen carefully.
‪The Party will be told that Ri Eung Ryeong
‪and 66 have been summarily executed.
‪If word gets out that we lost them
‪after the South handed them over to us,
‪we're all going to have to
‪take responsibility.
‪I've already spoken
‪with the delegation officials,
‪so make sure to keep your men quiet.
‪Understand?
‪Yes, sir.
‪-What are you talking about?
‪-Over there.
‪That's a person, right?
‪-What the heck?
‪-What is that?
‪That's a person, for crying out loud!
‪-Contact EMS and call for backup.
‪-Yes, sir.
‪-Sir, stay right here.
‪-Okay.
‪MYEONGJIN CENTRAL HOSPITAL
‪VIP1
‪UNIDENTIFIED PERSON
‪Goodness, Director General.
‪How do you feel?
‪I'm fine.
‪Start recording.
‪What's the rush?
‪Quickly, quickly.
‪This is how it is in the South.
‪You should get used to it too.
‪All right, then.
‪Let's start with the status of the ICBMs.
‪I have one last condition.
‪A condition?
‪After I give you all the information,
‪send me to Macau for asylum.
‪I'll think about it
‪depending on the quality
‪of the information.
‪So our understanding
‪is that the Strategic Rocket Force
‪is structured around a three-axis system.
‪Cholsan County, North Pyongan Province.
‪Chonchon County, Chagang Province.
‪And Kilju County, North Hamgyong Province.
‪At least 12 transporter erector launchers
‪are currently in service.
‪What about the current range?
‪Not only can they easily reach Guam,
‪but Alaska
‪and the US West Coast
‪are also within striking range.
‪How are they handling the fuel transition?
‪It's liquid-based right now,
‪but they're currently transitioning over
‪to solid fuel.
‪That's why I'm needed.
‪You see, all the information
‪is right in here.
‪VIP1
‪UNIDENTIFIED PERSON
‪PATIENT TRANSPORT
‪You kept your promise.
‪What are you going to do?
‪I'll take it from here.
‪It'd be a shame
‪to finish off an enemy so easily.
‪I need you to do one last thing for me.
‪No matter what happens,
‪promise me you'll survive.
‪What are you doing?
‪If you're done, go.
‪I wish you and your daughter…
‪a good life.
‪I'll stay alive too.
‪Good.
‪Stay alive…
‪no matter what.
‪COMMANDER'S OFFICE
‪CHEONSAN UNIT
‪So?
‪Who kidnapped Ri Eung Ryeong?
‪We have yet to identify the suspect, sir.
‪We're currently analyzing CCTV footage,
‪and we'll mobilize a team
‪once we track their movements.
‪Forget it. Let it go.
‪Sir?
‪We got all the information
‪we needed out of him.
‪It'd be a waste of taxpayer money
‪to keep him around longer.
‪It doesn't matter
‪whether he smuggles himself
‪out of the country or drops dead.
‪Either way, it's for the better.
‪But still…
‪Just do as I say.
‪That's an order.
‪Is this Macau?
‪Shit.
‪THE SEAS OF OUR HOMELAND
‪DO NOT TOLERATE LIES
‪THE COASTLINE IS THE FRONT LINE
‪OF NATIONAL DEFENSE!
‪No, it can't be.
‪F****** hell!
‪Don't move!
‪Stay right there!
‪-Stop!
‪-Stop right there!
‪Stop!
‪Stop right there!
‪JUHAK CONSTRUCTION CO., LTD.
‪CHO PYEONG-GYEON
‪It's me, sir.
‪Hey.
‪My goodness. Are you alive and well?
‪What made you call me all of a sudden?
‪I called to ask you a favor.
‪A favor?
‪What is it?
‪I need you to dissolve
‪Juhak Construction.
‪Goodness.
‪You haven't called in over a decade,
‪and that's what you ask me for?
‪It has to do with my daughter.
‪Please, sir.
‪My goodness, that poor thing.
‪Good heavens.
‪She must be really big now.
‪She's pretty like her mom, right?
‪I understand.
‪I've known her since she was born, so…
‪Juhak Construction, huh?
‪All right.
‪You got it.
‪Thank you.
‪Just wait a few days.
‪Juhak Construction is nothing.
‪I'll chop it up like a cucumber
‪and make a salad out of it.
‪You know this will cost you, right?
‪We're close, but we're professionals,
‪so I won't lower my fees.
‪You understand, right?
‪-Yes, I do.
‪-Good.
‪All right, then.
‪I'll call you back.
‪Thank you, sir.
‪Prosecutors have conducted
‪a surprise search and seizure
‪at Juhak Construction headquarters
‪and its affiliates earlier this morning.
‪-What's your business here?
‪-The investigation team
‪-We have a search and seizure warrant.
‪-is looking into suspicious cash flows
‪of tens of billions of won
‪between Juhak Construction affiliates
‪and political figures.
‪The said team believes the repeated,
‪large-scale fund transfers
‪were not legitimate business transactions
‪and is now tracing their source
‪and where they were ultimately used.
‪This investigation
‪was reportedly triggered
‪after the Financial Intelligence Unit
‪filed suspicious transaction reports
‪with the prosecution late last year.
‪Do you acknowledge the bribery charges?
‪Are the claims of redevelopment bias true?
‪-Please answer, Assemblyman!
‪-Let me pass.
‪-Please comment!
‪-We can do this another time.
‪Are you going on a trip abroad
‪after selling out your country?
‪-Arrest him.
‪-Yes, sir.
‪Let go of me!
‪Let go!
‪CAMBODIA
‪A court has issued an arrest warrant
‪for Chairman Ju Gang-chan
‪of Juhak Construction
‪on charges of kidnapping, murder,
‪and threatening national security.
‪The court cited the severity of the crimes
‪and the risk of evidence tampering
‪for its decision.
‪Chairman Ju
‪is reportedly hospitalized in Seoul.
‪Meanwhile, the prosecution has stated
‪it'll expand the investigation to include
‪the company's founding history
‪and the chairman's illegal activities.
‪Hye-ri, I know what you did.
‪Do you know Kim Min-ji?
‪Dang, the police came by the school.
‪-I heard his daughter left the country.
‪-Daughter of a murderer.
‪-Interpol is after you too.
‪-She's going to prison with her dad.
‪Ju Hye-ri is screwed.
‪He's coming out!
‪When did you start making contact
‪with North Korea?
‪Are the murder allegations true?
‪Are you aware that your daughter,
‪who fled abroad, has been arrested?
‪-Please say something!
‪-A comment, please!
‪Say something, asshole.
‪How've you been?
‪How does it feel
‪to get taken down by a dog?
‪You pulled out my teeth,
‪but I still have my claws, you bastard!
‪You should've returned
‪as soon as the mission was over.
‪Where have you been
‪looking like that?
‪Didn't you miss your daughter?
‪I had some business to take care of
‪for Min-ji's sake.
‪So?
‪Is the business taken care of?
‪Yes.
‪It's all over now.
‪Then it's time for me
‪to wrap things up as well.
‪Number 66…
‪must die.
‪The body of a man with a gunshot wound
‪was discovered by an herb collector
‪in the woods near the resort
‪where the North Korean delegation
‪was staying.
‪The deceased has been identified
‪as a man in his forties, surnamed Kim,
‪and police have launched an investigation
‪into the exact circumstances of his death.
‪BODY WITH GUNSHOT WOUND DISCOVERED
‪NEAR NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION LODGING
‪DECEASED IDENTIFIED AS MAN IN HIS FORTIES
‪INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY
‪HIGH-PROFILE WANTED FUGITIVE
‪COMPREHENSIVE PROFILE
‪YOUNGER YEARS
‪ESTIMATED CURRENT APPEARANCE
‪DELETE THIS PROFILE?
‪NO / YES
‪THE LATE KIM, THE LATE IM YU-JIN
‪I'm back.
‪I'm not going to run into your arms.
‪That'd be too cheesy.
‪You knew?
‪Sang-a told me.
‪She said you died.
‪But that you'd come back alive.
‪I promise
‪never to leave you again.
‪I'll always…
‪be right by your side.
‪Dad…
‪Do you know how worried I was?
‪I was so afraid
‪something had happened to you.
‪Thank you for coming back.
‪It's okay.
‪Wow, the flowers are so pretty.
‪I should come visit Mom more often.
‪Did Mom like flowers too?
‪Yeah.
‪Maybe that's why I'm pretty.
‪No.
‪You're pretty
‪because you take after your mom.
‪You're right.
‪I definitely don't get my looks from you.
‪Jeez.
‪What happens to us now?
‪From now on,
‪we're going to live completely new lives.
‪We'll live in a new place
‪with new identities.
‪We'll even have new names.
‪I see.
‪But I still want you to call me Min-ji.
‪Why? You don't want to change your name?
‪Mom gave me that name.
‪Okay, I will.
‪It feels like
‪we have our own little secret.
‪Doesn't it?
‪It won't be easy starting a new life.
‪Will you be okay?
‪I think it'll be fun.
‪This life wasn't much fun anyway.
‪I'll just consider this a new beginning.
‪Then how about a new beginning
‪as a model student?
‪You can study hard and go to college.
‪What?
‪Why do you get to decide that?
‪You don't even know what I want to become.
‪I can start learning now.
‪What do you want to be, Min-ji?
‪Me?
‪Maybe a singer?
‪What?
‪If you take after me,
‪singing isn't your thing.
‪What do you mean?
‪I'm tone-deaf!
‪Is that funny?
‪My gosh.
‪Mr. Kim.
‪And Min-ji.
‪Those are your new identities.
‪There's a manual inside the file,
‪so learn it inside and out.
‪Especially you, Min-ji.
‪"Kim Ji-min"?
‪You didn't even bother trying, did you?
‪Well, coming up with new names
‪isn't our job.
‪Thank you.
‪I hope I never see your face again.
‪Likewise.
‪I don't really want to
‪see your face either.
‪Me too.
‪What?
‪I've never seen you smile before, Mr. Kim.
‪This is him cracking up.
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah.
‪Here.
‪What is it?
‪I hope you grow up to be
‪someone great and admirable.
‪I guess it's kind of pretty.
‪Thank you.
‪He's much warmer than he seems.
‪We chose that together.
‪The three of you bought a single hairpin?
‪It's an expensive one.
‪-Do you like it?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Get back to work.
‪-Right.
‪-Yes, sir.
‪Mr. Kim!
‪Kim!
‪Take this.
‪It's not much.
‪It's to prevent bad luck.
‪I thought a new suit would be fitting
‪for your fresh start.
‪Wow, you're so lucky, Dad.
‪Come on, take it. It's heavy.
‪Thank you.
‪Iron out the wrinkles in your suit,
‪and the wrinkles in life
‪will iron themselves out.
‪I'll remember that.
‪Goodness, I wonder
‪when I'll get to see you again.
‪By the way,
‪we lived in the same neighborhood
‪but never even knew each other's names.
‪My name is
‪Im Ho-won.
‪Kim…
‪-Nice to meet you.
‪-Likewise.
‪Please take care.
‪-Take care.
‪-You too.
‪Goodbye, then.
‪ECOLOGICAL PARK
‪-Min-ji.
‪-Yeah?
‪Should we listen to some music?
‪PLAYLIST FOR CHERRY BLOSSOM DAYS
‪You know, people say you need new clothes
‪for a fresh start.
‪Shouldn't I get
‪some new clothes too, then?
‪Yeah, I should.
‪I'm unemployed now.
‪But you'll get a new job, right?
‪Come on.
‪All right.
‪I'll buy you new clothes when I get a job.
‪That's a promise, right?
‪I'm going to ask for something
‪really expensive.
‪All right.
‪Your homeroom teacher is awful.
‪How could he not even wish you good luck
‪when you're transferring?
‪I heard things have been tense at school
‪because of Hye-ri.
‪Yeah, I saw on social media that people
‪are calling it a school for criminals.
‪I know.
‪I guess
‪you're really transferring.
‪Yeah.
‪I'm sorry.
‪If only I hadn't messaged you that day…
‪You didn't do it on purpose.
‪It's okay.
‪Then…
‪Will you…
‪message me after you transfer?
‪I'll visit you.
‪I don't think
‪I can.
‪Right.
‪-I see.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪No, don't be sorry.
‪I think I should get going.
‪Already?
‪She's waiting for me.
‪Take care.
‪Here.
‪KIM MIN-JI
‪Will you…
‪remember my name?
‪Yeah.
‪Kim Min-ji.
‪How did it go?
‪Let's go.
‪This is it. What do you think?
‪Oh my gosh, it's so pretty!
‪-Come on, let's go.
‪-All right.
‪Hey, Kim!
‪Uncle?
‪-Hey.
‪Hey, what a great house.
‪Is it a rental or did you buy it?
‪Min-ji, did you do well on your exams?
‪Of course.
‪She's a level eight.
‪Wow, level eight?
‪-I'm jealous.
‪-What about Da-bin?
‪-She's healthy.
‪-That's all that matters.
‪Hey, Kim.
‪Hey, why are there so many boxes?
‪Do we have to move all of this?
‪Oh my.
‪Hey.
‪So you ‪do‪ own other clothes.
‪You look great.
‪I told you I have a lot of clothes.
‪-You look really rich.
‪-Do I?
‪Hey, hold on.
‪We're moving boxes,
‪and you came dressed like that?
‪Yeah.
‪Why?
‪Well, you know, it's a special day.
‪Have you lost your mind?
‪Be honest. You wore this
‪to avoid working, didn't you?
‪I'm tired. Stop talking to me.
‪You're tired?
‪Eat one of these, get an energy boost,
‪and start moving boxes.
‪And one for each of you
‪before you get to work.
‪Here.
‪And one for me too.
‪This tastes just like coffee.
‪It's good.
‪Just how many of those
‪do you have at home?
‪-Do you want a box?
‪-I sure do.
‪Are you moving in or not?
‪Coming!
‪Hey, let's finish up quickly and go eat.
‪-Hurry up and unload.
‪-Get a move on!
‪-Here we go.
‪-Let's go.
‪-Move some boxes, punk.
‪-Okay.
‪-All right.
‪-Let's go.
‪-Quickly, quickly.
‪-What are you doing?
‪-Hurry up now.
‪-Hurry up!
‪All right, here we go.
‪-That's the last one, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪Yeah, you little weasel.
‪You didn't even lift a finger.
‪All you did was carry the light boxes.
‪How can you look Min-ji in the eye?
‪Hey, Kim Min-ji-min… Ji-min.
‪Why are you laughing?
‪Do you want to see me get hurt
‪while carrying heavy boxes?
‪No, of course not.
‪Let's go eat. I'll take care of the rest.
‪Why bother? Let's just order ‪jjajangmyeon‪.
‪-‪Jjajangmyeon‪ is the best on moving days.
‪-Hey.
‪Why do you get to choose the menu?
‪Eat whatever Min-ji wants to have.
‪What do you want, Min-ji? You decide.
‪-Jjajangmyeon sounds good to--
‪-Did you say sushi? Okay.
‪Sushi sounds great.
‪Your daughter wants sushi.
‪You must really like sushi.
‪-Yeah, I love it.
‪-See?
‪Let's go have sushi.
‪-Get changed first.
‪-Let's go change.
‪-Han-soo, you're really something else.
‪-Okay.
‪You know, come to think of it,
‪you always wear the same outfit.
‪What are you looking at?
‪Darn it, I can't see without my glasses.
‪Hey, I want to see.
‪-Let me take a look.
‪-You can just look at that.
‪Oh, it's all here.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Gosh, there are so many items.
‪My stomach will be full of fish
‪swimming around.
‪Hey, Kim Min-ji-min.
‪You made a spectacular choice.
‪Order whatever you want.
‪-What are you having?
‪-I think I'll have--
‪Can we get one flounder…
‪Actually, make it five. What else?
‪Don't be shy.
‪And can we get five plates
‪of yellowfin tuna belly?
‪Here, have salmon. You like it, right?
‪You like it too.
‪One more salmon, please.
‪Make it five, please.
‪Do you want some too?
‪-Of course.
‪-Actually, make it ten.
‪Why are you eating with your hands?
‪That's how you eat sushi.
‪There's no eel here, what a shame.
‪Is it good?
‪Yeah, it's dangerously good.
‪He wasn't asking you, Uncle.
‪Sorry.
‪It's good.
‪Eat up.
‪-Okay.
‪Eat up, you guys.
‪Okay.
‪-Sir, you forgot the monkfish liver.
‪-What else do you want?
‪A new neighborhood, a new school…
‪and a new name I don't like.
‪Min-ji, come have breakfast!
‪Kim Min-ji!
‪I'm late.
‪A lot of things have changed,
‪but my dad and I haven't ‪changed
‪all ‪that ‪much.
‪I'll eat after I get back. Save me some.
‪Okay, I will.
‪Be safe.
‪And don't get into any fights!
‪I won't!
‪Except for my dad laughing more often now.
‪Hello, ma'am.
‪Pure hearts, pure manners.
‪Join Pure Taekwondo.
‪-And my uncles are still the same.
‪-We're offering free trial classes.
‪Thank you.
‪Hello.
‪-Look who's back.
‪-We're offering free trial classes.
‪-Who's that man over there?
‪-It's not on the flyer,
‪but we play dodgeball,
‪and there are prizes, so come by, okay?
‪-Hello, ma'am.
‪-Cross slowly!
‪Please cross the street now.
‪Pure Taekwondo
‪is located on the third floor.
‪Feel free to drop by
‪during the free trial period.
‪Hello, ma'am.
‪Should we stop him?
‪Leave him be. It's a nice sight.
‪I bet he was a big club-goer.
‪POLICE
‪The weather is so nice.
‪I know, right?
‪It was really cold not too long ago.
‪-Please enjoy.
‪-Thank you.
‪Let's eat.
‪This looks good.
‪Hold on. We need to take a photo.
‪Sang-a hangs out with me sometimes.
‪Sang-a.
‪You're here to keep an eye on me, right?
‪No, I'm not.
‪You think you're special?
‪No.
‪Who saved your life?
‪You did.
‪Then who should you be thanking?
‪You?
‪So who should pay for this?
‪Right, I should pay.
‪Dig in.
‪Thank you.
‪How are things with your dad?
‪Is he more affectionate than before?
‪No, he's still the same.
‪Right.
‪That's not really who he is, is it?
‪It's totally not him.
‪Any good news lately, Sang-a?
‪-He was like, "You can't date yet."
‪-Really?
‪I'm not surprised.
‪Allow me to present today's special.
‪These would be good for when I do this.
‪Do you have regular glasses
‪instead of sunglasses?
‪Who are you?
‪I usually don't show this to anyone,
‪but here goes.
‪"Brother Monkey, what's gotten into you?"
‪Hello.
‪My name is Kim. Nice to meet you.
‪In my opinion, this case is…
‪Rock and roll.
‪Hey, Han-soo, Jin-cheol.
‪You think Min-ji will approve?
‪Probably not.
‪Hey, what do you think?
‪They suit me, right?
‪-You look weird.
‪Damn it.
‪Just kidding.
‪You look like Tony Leung Chiu-wai.
‪Tony Leung Chiu-wai, my foot.
‪He looks like a brewery owner.
‪Hey, you look like a middle-aged man
‪desperate to look young.
‪That's what we are.
‪Right.
‪We're middle-aged men.
‪Middle-aged men with glasses.
‪Now that I'm wearing glasses again
‪after a while,
‪I feel like
‪they're weighing my shoulders down.
‪Should we take them off?
‪No. It's better to be
‪middle-aged men with glasses.
‪-Let's go.
‪-Okay.
‪-Goodbye, sir.
‪-Oh, goodbye.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Goodbye.
‪-Have a good day.
‪-Take care.
‪-There wasn't much to choose from.
‪-You tried on 145 pairs.
‪It feels pretty good
‪to wear new glasses though.
‪Yeah, I feel like I could fly!
‪Hey, mister.
‪You should never mess with
‪middle-aged men with glasses.
‪-Yeah, someone could get someone hurt.
‪-Who?
‪The one who messed with them
‪or the middle-aged men with glasses?
‪I'm not sure.
‪All dads in the world
‪are just regular people.
‪-They work to support their families,
‪-What's with the color?
‪-and they're afraid of moms.
‪-Guys, check it out.
‪-And sometimes after work‪…
‪-Did you ask for these?
‪They're transition lenses.
‪-…‪they come home with smelly feet.
‪-I didn't ask for these though.
‪They give off a middle-aged man vibe.
‪Man, these are slick.
‪It may be hard to believe, but my dad
‪is also just a regular middle-aged man.
‪Well,
‪as long as no one messes with me.
‪HAPPINESS ROAD, HAENGBOK-RO
‪BAEKHO LABOR AGENCY
‪Oh, I almost forgot.
‪I think my dad's getting a new job.
‪Someone he knew back in the day
‪introduced him to it.
‪Juhak Construction is nothing.
‪I'll chop it up like a cucumber
‪and make a salad out of it.
‪You know this will cost you, right?
‪3RD FLOOR
‪May I help you?
‪Excuse me.
‪I'm here for an interview--
‪Check and check!
‪I just checked your résumé, Kim!
‪But you know,
‪I'm not sure if I can trust this.
‪Now then.
‪Shall we start
‪the interview?
‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪STAY TUNED FOR A BONUS SCENE
‪BONUS SCENE
‪IN 2006, THERE WAS A FAMOUS TRIO
‪IN THE CHEONSAN UNIT
‪CHEONSAN
‪Korea's iron teeth!
‪They're unbreakable!
‪PARK JIN-CHEOL
‪YOON KYUNG-HO
‪SUNG HAN-SOO
‪CHOI DAE-HOON
‪KIM
‪SO JI-SUB
‪AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‪Subtitle translation by: